{
    "subject": "resource/James_Cronin",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1931",
    "human_readable": "James Cronin was born in 1931.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8586227893829346,
            "question": "In what year was James Cronin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7619442939758301,
            "question": "During which decade was James Cronin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465253472328186,
            "question": "Who was born in the year 1931?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7414523363113403,
            "question": "What was the year of James Cronin's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7187070846557617,
            "question": "What is the birth year of James Cronin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089584469795227,
            "question": "Is James Cronin a person born in the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6480631232261658,
            "question": "What year is associated with James Cronin's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190114617347717,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance associated with the year of James Cronin's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4385426938533783,
            "question": "How old would James Cronin be if he were alive today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43510082364082336,
            "question": "When did James Cronin come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Cronin was born in 1931.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5744_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would James Cronin be if he were alive today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5744_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical significance associated with the year of James Cronin's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5744_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year is associated with James Cronin's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5744_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5744_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that James Cronin was born on September 29, 1931. Therefore, the statement \"James Cronin was born in 1931\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}